{
    "subject": "Noboru_Iguchi",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "RoboGeisha",
    "human_readable": "Noboru Iguchi directed the film RoboGeisha.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8816359043121338,
            "question": "Who directed the film RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8281885981559753,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Noboru Iguchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6032238602638245,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Noboru Iguchi you know about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.553564727306366,
            "question": "What other directors are known for similar film styles to Noboru Iguchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5362229943275452,
            "question": "What genre might the film RoboGeisha fall into given its director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48118171095848083,
            "question": "Where might one find information about the plot of RoboGeisha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4696243107318878,
            "question": "Would you recommend RoboGeisha based on the director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43622061610221863,
            "question": "Are there any recurring themes or elements in Noboru Iguchi's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4014137387275696,
            "question": "What year was RoboGeisha released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2765048146247864,
            "question": "Has RoboGeisha received any critical acclaim?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noboru Iguchi directed the film RoboGeisha.",
            "html": "yago_17988_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was RoboGeisha released?",
            "html": "yago_17988_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any recurring themes or elements in Noboru Iguchi's films?",
            "html": "yago_17988_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you recommend RoboGeisha based on the director?",
            "html": "yago_17988_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17988_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provide information that supports the claim, specifically from the reviews and articles about the film RoboGeisha, which mention Noboru Iguchi as the director."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Noboru Iguchi directed the film \"RoboGeisha,\" supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}